budgetgadgets.com 2011-11-04

# BudgetGadgets.com

|    | Privacy Policy - www.BudgetGadgets.com

|   
---  
|  |   | BudgetGadgets.com Privacy Policy  (Updated 11/25/2010)  
---|---  
|    
---  
By visiting the BudgetGadgets.com website, you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Notice. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Notice, please do not use the Site. Each time you use the Site, you should check the date of this Privacy Notice (which appears above) and review any changes that have been made since your last visit to the Site.  
   
Throughout BudgetGadgets.com's years of operation, we have developed relationships with our customers based on respect and integrity. We're aware of the trust and confidence you demonstrate when you visit the Site and provide us with information. This Privacy Notice is posted to demonstrate our leadership in online security and customer service practices. We treat your information with the same honesty and sensitivity that we have displayed throughout our company's history.  
   
**1\. Personal Information Collected By BudgetGadgets.com**  
  
BudgetGadgets.com uses information that we collect from our visitors and customers to personalize and improve your visit and shopping experience at the Site. We gather the following types of information:

I **nformation You Give to Us:** We Collect Personal Information that is provided by Site users. "Personal Information" includes your name, address, telephone number, credit or debit card information, e-mail address, date of birth, IP address. Personal Information is collected when you establish an account with us, place an order on the Site, participate in a contest, sweepstakes or on-line survey, or when you communicate with any of our departments such as customer service, sales or technical services through the Site, telephone, mail or fax. In some instances, we may obtain other people's names and email addresses that you may choose to provide as part of our "email a friend" feature.

**Web Beacons:** We (or service providers on our behalf) may collect information from visits to the Site through the use of "Web Beacons." Web Beacons are web page elements which may employ cookie technology that enable us to record data about visits to or transactions made on the Site. This information is sometimes known as "clickstream data." We may use this data to analyze trends and statistics to improve your online experience or our customer service. No Personal Information is collected through the use of Web Beacons on the Site.

**Cookies:** Through the use of cookies, we may also collect and analyze the IP address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as your browser type and version; operating system and platform; purchase history; confirmation when you open e-mail that we send you; and the URLs which lead you to and around the Site including the date and time. You can generally set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie. Software is also available from third parties which will allow you to visit the Site without providing this information. You are welcome to use the Site if you use such software but we will not be able to offer you our personalized services and we will be unable to accept any online orders from you.

**Orders:** If you place an order through the Site, you will be required to provide contact, billing, and payment information.

**Catalog Requests and Email Newsletter Subscriptions:** Upon placing an order through the Site, you will automatically begin receiving both the BudgetGadgets.com catalog and the BudgetGadgets.com email newsletter, based on the Personal Information you have provided, unless you opt-out of receiving such communications. If you request an email newsletter subscription, we will send you an email confirming your request. This confirmation process allows you to unsubscribe if you change your mind and decide not to join the list. Furthermore, the confirmation email will alert you if someone else has entered your email address into our email newsletter subscription list. In order to make our email newsletters more relevant and useful to you, our servers may receive a confirmation when you open an email message from BudgetGadgets.com.

**Sweepstakes Entrants:** From time to time, we may run sweepstakes. If you enter sweepstakes sponsored by us, we employ a double opt-in subscription program. Upon registration, a confirmation email will be sent to the email address you provide to us in connection with your entry which will include instructions, or a link to instructions, for completing the subscription process. You will not be entered until you click through the link in the email we send to you or otherwise follow the instructions contained therein. In order to make our sweepstakes more relevant to you, our servers may receive a confirmation when you open an email message from us.  

**2\. Use of Information Collected By Use**  
We use this information in an effort to improve your experience on the Site, to provide services to you and to communicate with you about information that you request. We may also use this information to help us target specific offers to you, to help us develop and improve our Site, and to tailor our Site to your interests.  
   
**3\. Affiliate Programs**  
We maintain relationships with third party affiliate websites. Although we do not and cannot control the activities of the third parties that operate such websites, we will cease doing business with any affiliate that engages in abusive practices, including, for example, spam, trademark infringement, predatory means of attracting visitors, or unlawful activities. To report abuse by an affiliate, please contact our Affiliate Manager via email at affiliates@BudgetGadgets.com.  
   
**4\. Children and Privacy**  
The Site is a general audience website and is not directed to children under the age of 13. We will never knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide us with personally identifiable information of any kind whatsoever. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 13 and has submitted Personal Information without verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable information from our files. We understand that children may not fully understand all of the provisions of this Privacy Notice or make informed decisions about the choices that are made available to adult users of the Site. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be familiar with the websites they visit. BudgetGadgets.com does not sell products to persons under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you are required seek the consent of your parent or guardian to purchase products from the Site.  
   
**5\. Security**  
  
We employ 128-bit encryption technology in all areas of the Site which require you to provide your personal or account information, including those areas related to online ordering, order status, catalog request and contest forms. The Site utilizes industry-standard firewalls and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to allow for the encryption of potentially sensitive Personal Information, such as your name, address and credit card number.

You should recognize, however, that no computer system is fully secure and that there are inherent risks associated with Internet transactions. To make sure you have the latest security features on your browser, you may want to download the most recent version of your favorite browser, which should have full SSL support.  

**6\. Information Updates**  
If your name, e-mail or postal address, telephone number or other Personal Information changes, you may update your information according to below link:  
<http://www.budgetgadgets.com/account.php>  
   
**7\. Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Notice, please e-mail us at
